Guide to the Oswald G. Villard Papers
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Yunchun, Song, 1991 (Box 113, Folder 43)
- Yunguang, Qiu, 1991 (Box 113, Folder 44)
- Zhang, Xia Yan, 1991 (Box 113, Folder 45)
- Zheng, Zhou, 1991 (Box 113, Folder 46)
- Zhijin, Chen, 1991 (Box 113, Folder 47)
- Zhi Ling, Peng, 1991 (Box 113, Folder 48)
- Ziang, Guo Di, 1991 (Box 113, Folder 49)
- Translators (Box 113, Folder 50)
- Haoyi, Zheng, 1992 (Box 113, Folder 51)
- Chinese Students, 1991 (Box 113, Folder 52)
- Shao Ming, Chao, 1991 (Box 113, Folder 53)
- Gang, Hu Zhi, 1991 (Box 113, Folder 54)
- Miscellaneous Chinese correspondence (mostly photocopies) (Box 113, Folder 55)
- Stanford University – SRI relations, 1989 (Box 113, Folder 56)
- Stanford University Center for Telecommunications, 1989 (Box 113, Folder 57)
- Stanford University correspondence, 1984-1986 (Box 113, Folder 58)
- Stanford University correspondence, 1987 (Box 113, Folder 59)
- SRI publicity committee, 1991 (Box 113, Folder 60)
- SRI Qualifying Exams for RMS, 1988 (Box 113, Folder 61)
- Soong, T. T., 1989 (Box 113, Folder 62)
- Smith, Vernon (BBC), 1987 (Box 113, Folder 63)
- Smith, Ernest K., 1988 (Box 113, Folder 64)
- Skilling, Hugh H. (EE), 1990 (Box 113, Folder 65)
- Stanford University SEL project, 1987 (Box 113, Folder 66)
- Stanford University subcontract C-10474, 1986 (Box 113, Folder 67)
- SRC (Stanford University Radio Club) correspondence, 1985-1987 (Box 114, Folder 1)
- SRC, 1983 (Box 114, Folder 2)
- SRC Fund Statements and Expenditures, 1981-1983 (Box 114, Folder 3)
- SRC Hewlitt-Packard, 1967 (Box 114, Folder 4)
- SRC, 1972-1984 (Box 114, Folder 5)
- SRC Equipment, 1982-1983 (Box 114, Folder 6)
- SRC Heintz Gift, 1975 (Box 114, Folder 7)
- Villard Stanford University Faculty Record, 1961-1968 (Box 114, Folder 8)
- Stanford University Electrical Engineering Dept. Faculty reports, 1986-1990 (Box 114, Folder 9)
- Stanford University Electrical Engineering Dept. Faculty reports, 1973-1985 (Box 114, Folder 10)
- Stanford University Electrical Engineering Dept. Miscellaneous class data, 1965-1982 (Box 114, Folder 11)
- Stanford University Electrical Engineering Dept. faculty Miscellaneous, 1985-1991 (Box 114, Folder 12)
- STAR lab correspondence, 1981-1989 (Box 114, Folder 13)
- STAR lab correspondence & report, Peterson bibliography (Box 114, Folder 14)
- Steele, Varrick (RFE/RL), 1985-1987 (Box 114, Folder 15)
- Stone, Ross (AP/S newsletter), 1988-1989 (Box 114, Folder 16)
- Straub, Erwin (RFE/RL), 1984-1990 (Box 114, Folder 17)
- Stutzman, Warren, 1988 (Box 114, Folder 18)
- Sullivan, W. T. (Box 114, Folder 19)
- Superconductivity memos, 1987 (Box 114, Folder 20)
- Superior Electric Co. correspondence, 1984-1985 (Box 114, Folder 21)
- Superior Electric Co. BOD membership, 1982-1983 (Box 114, Folder 22)
- Sutherland, D. A., 1989 (Box 114, Folder 23)
- Shortwave Listeners from Designated countries, 1991 (Box 114, Folder 24)
- Shortwave Listener Survey, 1991 (Box 114, Folder 25)
- Swan, Robert, 1990-1991 (Box 114, Folder 26)
- Swedish DX Federation (Box 114, Folder 27)
- Sylten, Hans (Gould, Inc.), 1988 (Box 114, Folder 28)
- Tape, Gerald, 1984-1985 (Box 114, Folder 29)
- Techniloop Antenna, 1988 (Box 114, Folder 30)
- Thomas, Alec (BBC), 1987 (Box 114, Folder 31)
- Titterton, Paul, 1989 (Box 114, Folder 32)
- Trip to Europe, 5/9-25/1989 (Box 114, Folder 33)
- Trip, 6/15-17/1987 (Box 114, Folder 34)
- Fallis trip, 11/17/1987 (Box 114, Folder 35)
- Trip to Europe, 1987 (Box 114, Folder 36)
- Pell RFE visit, 10/16/1987 (Box 114, Folder 37)
- Tuma, Thomas visit, 10/1985 (Box 114, Folder 38)
- URSI Constitution Bylaws, 1968 (Box 114, Folder 39)
- URSI talk notes, photographs, transparencies, 1/4/1991 (Box 114, Folder 40)
- URSI meetings, 1991-1994 (Box 114, Folder 41)
- URSI reprints, 1989 (Box 114, Folder 42)
- URSI seminar talk, 1/4-6/1989 (Box 114, Folder 43)
- Villard SRI President's Award, 12/1988 (Box 114, Folder 44)
- Villard Performance Review, 1987-1989 (Box 114, Folder 45)
- Villard personal biographies, publications, photographs, 1964-1991 (Box 114, Folder 46)
- Villard article for World Radio & TV Handbook, 1990 (Box 114, Folder 47)
- WRTH, 1991 (Box 114, Folder 48)
- Wright-Patterson Air Force Base, 1988 (Box 114, Folder 49)
- Wysocki, Stefan (RFE/RL) correspondence, 1987-1991 (Box 114, Folder 50)
- Yeh, Kung C. NAE nomination, 1990-1991 (Box 114, Folder 51)
- Yeh, Kung C. AGU fellow nomination (Box 114, Folder 52)
- Yameen, Mohammed, 1990 (Box 114, Folder 53)
- Williams, Robert S., 1990 (Box 114, Folder 54)
- Bound reprints (Box 114, Folder 55)
- LDE reprints, reports, copies, notes, 1963-1979 (Box 115, Folder 1)
- LDE ARRC talk, 9/6/1980 (Box 115, Folder 2)
- LDE J37, 1980 (Box 115, Folder 3)
- LDE article on Field Alligned LDEs, 1979-1981 (Box 115, Folder 4)
- LDE QST article X04, 1980 (Box 115, Folder 5)
- LDE QST article X04, 1980 (Box 115, Folder 6)
- LDE QST article X04, 1980 (Box 115, Folder 7)
- LDE URSI talk references (Box 115, Folder 8)
- LDE to be used URSI material (Box 115, Folder 9)
- LDE paper ONR H6804 figures, 1976-1977 (Box 115, Folder 10)
- LDE paper ONR H6804 & material, 1976 (Box 115, Folder 11)
- LDE Blakeslee correspondence, 1976-1977 (Box 115, Folder 12)
- IEEE general correspondence, 1963-1985 (Box 115, Folder 13)
- IEEE nomination forms, 1965-1969 (Box 115, Folder 14)
- IEEE nomination Angell, James B. (Box 115, Folder 15)
- IEEE nomination Ayer, William E., 1965-1968 (Box 115, Folder 16)
- IEEE nomination Barnum. James R., 1970 (Box 115, Folder 17)
- IEEE nomination Battes, Robert J., 1970 (Box 115, Folder 18)
- IEEE nomination Booker, Henry G., 1984 (Box 115, Folder 19)
- IEEE nomination Bowles, Kenneth L., 1965 (Box 115, Folder 20)
- IEEE nomination Clark, Clayton, 1969 (Box 115, Folder 21)
- IEEE nomination Clarke, Kenneth K., 1968 (Box 115, Folder 22)
- IEEE nomination Cooley, Donald W., 1985 (Box 115, Folder 23)
- IEEE nomination Crawford, Frederick W., 1971 (Box 115, Folder 24)
- IEEE nomination Da Rose, Aldo, 1973-1975 (Box 115, Folder 25)
- IEEE nomination Davies, Kenneth, 1983 (Box 115, Folder 26)
- IEEE nomination Dyce, Rolf B., 1966 (Box 115, Folder 27)
- IEEE nomination Egan, Raymond D., 1965 (Box 115, Folder 28)
- IEEE nomination Ferraro, Anthony J., 1970 (Box 115, Folder 29)
- IEEE nomination Flugge-Lotz, Irmgard, 1962 (Box 115, Folder 30)
- IEEE nomination Franklin, Gene F., 1967 (Box 115, Folder 31)
- IEEE nomination Fraser-Smith, Anthony, 1986 (Box 115, Folder 32)
- IEEE nomination Gibbons, James F., 1970 (Box 115, Folder 33)
- IEEE nomination Gibbons, James, 1968 (Box 115, Folder 34)
- IEEE nomination Harman, Willis W., 1964 (Box 115, Folder 35)
- IEEE nomination Hedlund, Donald A., 1965 (Box 115, Folder 36)
- IEEE nomination Howard, Henry T., 1984-1988 (Box 115, Folder 37)
- IEEE nomination Hunsucker, Robert D., 1991 (Box 115, Folder 38)
- IEEE nomination Jamieson, John A., 1970 (Box 115, Folder 39)
- IEEE nomination Kailath, Thomas, 1969 (Box 115, Folder 40)
- IEEE nomination Kelso, John M., 1972 (Box 115, Folder 41)
- IEEE nomination Kino, Gordon S., 1961 (Box 115, Folder 42)
- IEEE nomination Lacy, Peter D., 1966 (Box 115, Folder 43)
- IEEE nomination Leeson, David B., 1987 (Box 115, Folder 44)
- IEEE nomination Linvill, W. K., 1966 (Box 115, Folder 45)
- IEEE nomination Liu, Chao Han, 1978 (Box 115, Folder 46)
- IEEE nomination Mallinckrodt, A. J., 1967 (Box 115, Folder 47)
- IEEE nomination Mason, Fred L., 1966 (Box 115, Folder 48)
- IEEE nomination McCluskey, E. J., 1969 (Box 115, Folder 49)
- IEEE nomination McWhorter, Malcolm M., 1966 (Box 116, Folder 1)
- IEEE nomination Nanevicz, Joseph E., 1978-1982 (Box 116, Folder 2)
- IEEE nomination Quate, Calvin F., 1963 (Box 116, Folder 3)
- IEEE nomination Reynolds, Donald K., 1965 (Box 116, Folder 4)
- IEEE nomination Ross, William J., 1971 (Box 116, Folder 5)
- IEEE nomination Shearman, Edwin D., 1981 (Box 116, Folder 6)
- IEEE nomination Siegman, Anthony E., 1964 (Box 116, Folder 7)
- IEEE nomination Simpson, Richard A., 1983 (Box 116, Folder 8)
- IEEE nomination Smith, Ralph J., 1968 (Box 116, Folder 9)
- IEEE nomination Steele, John G., 1967-1972 (Box 116, Folder 10)
- IEEE nomination Swarm, H. Myron, 1965 (Box 116, Folder 11)
- IEEE nomination Sweeney, Lawrence E. Jr., 1986-1991 (Box 116, Folder 12)
- IEEE nomination Tyler, George L., 1987 (Box 116, Folder 13)
- IEEE nomination Utlaut, William F., 1969 (Box 116, Folder 14)
- IEEE nomination Waterman, Alan T., 1965 (Box 116, Folder 15)
- IEEE nomination Widow, Bernard, 1968 (Box 116, Folder 16)
- IEEE nomination Yeh, C. K., 1973 (Box 116, Folder 17)
- Inan, Aziz, 1984-1988 (Box 116, Folder 18)
- Inan, Umran, 1988 (Box 116, Folder 19)
- Information Express, 1991 (Box 116, Folder 20)
- Intensatronics, 1991 (Box 116, Folder 21)
- Interceptor Loop Antenna, 1988 (Box 116, Folder 22)
- Interference-Reducing Personal Radiation Processors… article, 1986 (Box 116, Folder 23)
- Ionospheric Modification, 1987 (Box 116, Folder 24)
- IR&D Creativity Review Panel, 1989 (Box 116, Folder 25)
- IR&D Creativity Review Panel meeting, 2/1/1990 (Box 116, Folder 26)
- IR&D Creativity Review Panel meeting, 1/17/1990 (Box 116, Folder 27)
- IR&D Creativity Review Panel reviews, 1988-1989 (Box 116, Folder 28)
- IR&D Creativity Review Panel, 1989-1990 (Box 116, Folder 29)
- IR&D Creativity Review Panel material, 1988-1990 (Box 116, Folder 30)
- IR&D Creativity Review Panel meeting minutes, 1989 (Box 116, Folder 31)
- IR&D Creativity Review Panel Information request forms (Box 116, Folder 32)
- IR&D Creativity Review Panel meeting, 9/14/1989 (Box 116, Folder 33)
- IR&D reports, 1984-1986 (Box 116, Folder 34)
- IR&D reports, 1989-1990 (Box 116, Folder 35)
- Books, mostly Soviet military philosophy in translation (Box 116, Folder 36)
- Books, mostly on antennas, bound ONR unclassified reports vol. 1-3 (Box 117, Folder 1)
- Bound ONR unclassified reports vol. 4-8 (Box 118, Folder 1)
- Transparencies (Box 119, Folder 1)
- Obsolete Items, 1979-1980 (Box 119, Folder 2)
- RCS, 11/21/1979 (Box 119, Folder 3)
- Obsolete Transparencies (Box 119, Folder 4)
- Transparencies, 11/19/1979 (Box 119, Folder 5)
- Nicolai - Status, 11/13/1979 (Box 119, Folder 6)
- RCS, 7/13/1979 (Box 119, Folder 7)
- RCS material, 4/16/1979 (Box 119, Folder 8)
- Basics (Box 119, Folder 9)
- Calculations (Box 119, Folder 10)
- Bahr-Robinson, 1979 (Box 119, Folder 11)
- CSI tests report, 6/6/1979 (Box 119, Folder 12)
- History of RCS (Box 119, Folder 13)
- RCS, 11/21/1979 (Box 119, Folder 14)
- Detritus, 1979 (Box 119, Folder 15)
- AJB/OGV, 1/29/1980 (Box 119, Folder 16)
- RCS Calculations (Box 119, Folder 17)
- Conclusions (Box 119, Folder 18)
- Polaroids (Box 119, Folder 19)
- Bratislava Recordings notes (Box 119, Folder 20)
- Austrian Trip Log notes, 1984 (Box 119, Folder 21)
- Innovative Technological Initiatives Ad Hoc Group meeting, 1/4/1985 (Box 119, Folder 22)
- QST LDE article #2, 2/1970 (Box 119, Folder 23)
- Villard LDE talk at Stanford University, 5/5/1980 (Box 119, Folder 24)
- Marleen's LDE Miscellaneous, 1968-1969 (Box 119, Folder 25)
- LDE Questionaires, North & South California DX Clubs, 1969 (Box 119, Folder 26)
- QST LDE article #3, 11/1970 (Box 119, Folder 27)
- LDE photographs, sonograms, 5/27/1969 (Box 119, Folder 28)
- LDE Data Summary Sheets (Box 119, Folder 29)
- QST LDE article #15/1969 (Box 119, Folder 30)
- Miscellaneous audiovisual material; 16 mm film, audio tape (reels, cassettes, microcassettes), microfilm, shortwave radio science kit (Box 120, Folder 1)
- LDE Santa Maria Test Summary (Box 121, Folder 1)
- LDE Perception Tests, Tally Sheets (Box 121, Folder 2)
- LDE Perception Tests (Box 121, Folder 3)
- LDE Perception Tests Plot Masters (Box 121, Folder 4)
- LDE Perception Tests (Box 121, Folder 5)
- LDE general, reprints, etc. (Box 121, Folder 6)
- LDE, 5/5/1979 (Box 121, Folder 7)